export const SubtractionQuestion = {
  question1: {
      question: "6 - 2 = ?",
      options: [3, 4, 5, 6],
      answer: 4
  },
  question2: {
      question: "7 - 1 = ?",
      options: [4, 5, 6, 7],
      answer: 6
  },
  question3: {
      question: "14 - 3 = ?",
      options: [9, 10, 11, 12],
      answer: 11
  },
  question4: {
      question: "16 - 6 = ?",
      options: [8, 9, 10, 11],
      answer: 10
  },
  question5: {
      question: "13 - 2 = ?",
      options: [10, 11, 12, 13],
      answer: 11
  },
  question6: {
      question: "10 - 5 = ?",
      options: [4, 5, 6, 7],
      answer: 5
  },
  question7: {
      question: "20 - 15 = ?",
      options: [4, 5, 6, 7],
      answer: 5
  },
  question8: {
      question: "25 - 10 = ?",
      options: [14, 15, 16, 17],
      answer: 15
  },
  question9: {
      question: "30 - 20 = ?",
      options: [8, 9, 10, 11],
      answer: 10
  },
  question10: {
      question: "12 - 6 = ?",
      options: [4, 5, 6, 7],
      answer: 6
  },
  question11: {
      question: "18 - 9 = ?",
      options: [7, 8, 9, 10],
      answer: 9
  },
  question12: {
      question: "22 - 12 = ?",
      options: [8, 9, 10, 11],
      answer: 10
  },
  question13: {
      question: "15 - 3 = ?",
      options: [10, 11, 12, 13],
      answer: 12
  },
  question14: {
      question: "9 - 4 = ?",
      options: [4, 5, 6, 7],
      answer: 5
  },
  question15: {
      question: "28 - 8 = ?",
      options: [19, 20, 21, 22],
      answer: 20
  },
  question16: {
      question: "50 - 25 = ?",
      options: [20, 21, 22, 25],
      answer: 25
  },
  question17: {
      question: "40 - 30 = ?",
      options: [8, 9, 10, 11],
      answer: 10
  },
  question18: {
      question: "33 - 11 = ?",
      options: [21, 22, 23, 24],
      answer: 22
  },
  question19: {
      question: "14 - 7 = ?",
      options: [5, 6, 7, 8],
      answer: 7
  },
  question20: {
      question: "20 - 14 = ?",
      options: [5, 6, 7, 8],
      answer: 6
  },
  question21: {
      question: "29 - 19 = ?",
      options: [8, 9, 10, 11],
      answer: 10
  },
  question22: {
      question: "16 - 4 = ?",
      options: [10, 11, 12, 13],
      answer: 12
  },
  question23: {
      question: "27 - 18 = ?",
      options: [7, 8, 9, 10],
      answer: 9
  },
  question24: {
      question: "13 - 5 = ?",
      options: [7, 8, 9, 10],
      answer: 8
  },
  question25: {
      question: "25 - 5 = ?",
      options: [18, 19, 20, 21],
      answer: 20
  },
  question26: {
      question: "11 - 6 = ?",
      options: [4, 5, 6, 7],
      answer: 5
  },
  question27: {
      question: "34 - 14 = ?",
      options: [19, 20, 21, 22],
      answer: 20
  },
  question28: {
      question: "50 - 20 = ?",
      options: [29, 30, 31, 32],
      answer: 30
  },
  question29: {
      question: "44 - 4 = ?",
      options: [38, 39, 40, 41],
      answer: 40
  },
  question30: {
      question: "70 - 30 = ?",
      options: [39, 40, 41, 42],
      answer: 40
  },
  question31: {
      question: "48 - 20 = ?",
      options: [28, 29, 30, 31],
      answer: 28
  },
  question32: {
      question: "100 - 50 = ?",
      options: [40, 50, 60, 70],
      answer: 50
  },
  question33: {
      question: "21 - 9 = ?",
      options: [11, 12, 13, 14],
      answer: 12
  },
  question34: {
      question: "17 - 7 = ?",
      options: [8, 9, 10, 11],
      answer: 10
  },
  question35: {
      question: "5 - 2 = ?",
      options: [2, 3, 4, 5],
      answer: 3
  },
  question36: {
      question: "30 - 10 = ?",
      options: [18, 19, 20, 21],
      answer: 20
  },
  question37: {
      question: "36 - 6 = ?",
      options: [28, 29, 30, 31],
      answer: 30
  },
  question38: {
      question: "45 - 5 = ?",
      options: [38, 39, 40, 41],
      answer: 40
  },
  question39: {
      question: "60 - 15 = ?",
      options: [43, 44, 45, 46],
      answer: 45
  },
  question40: {
      question: "80 - 50 = ?",
      options: [28, 29, 30, 31],
      answer: 30
  },
  question41: {
      question: "14 - 4 = ?",
      options: [9, 10, 11, 12],
      answer: 10
  },
  question42: {
      question: "10 - 3 = ?",
      options: [5, 6, 7, 8],
      answer: 7
  },
  question43: {
      question: "8 - 3 = ?",
      options: [4, 5, 6, 7],
      answer: 5
  },
  question44: {
      question: "2 - 1 = ?",
      options: [1, 2, 3, 4],
      answer: 1
  },
  question45: {
      question: "90 - 30 = ?",
      options: [55, 60, 57, 58],
      answer: 60
  },
  question46: {
      question: "35 - 15 = ?",
      options: [19, 20, 21, 22],
      answer: 20
  },
  question47: {
      question: "16 - 8 = ?",
      options: [6, 7, 8, 9],
      answer: 8
  },
  question48: {
      question: "33 - 20 = ?",
      options: [12, 13, 14, 15],
      answer: 13
  },
  question49: {
      question: "27 - 7 = ?",
      options: [19, 20, 21, 22],
      answer: 20
  },
  question50: {
      question: "100 - 99 = ?",
      options: [1, 2, 3, 4],
      answer: 1
  }
};

